mobilarian.com 2019-02-23

# Mobilarian Forum - Privacy Policy

Mobilarian Forum is committed to providing a safe and secure web site. We are dedicated to safeguarding all personal information collected online and to helping our users learn how to exercise control over personal information while exploring the Internet. To help ensure a rewarding online experience for all users, we provide this summary of our information practices. This privacy notice governs the collection and use of information at Mobilarian Forum.

As we continue to offer different types of content and services, we may modify our practices from time to time. However, we will treat all personal information we collect in accordance with the privacy notice in effect at the time the information is collected.

### THE INFORMATION WE OBTAIN

Basic User Information

Mobilarian Forum is mainly a discussion forum and like any other forum we require a user who wishes to participate in the forums to supply a user name, password and email address during registration. At that same time we also ask for the user birth date to verify the age of the user in compliance with the COPPA laws.

User Profile Information

Our web site also serves as online social networking community that connects people of the same interest for communicating, sharing and making new friends. To accomplish this, a registered user creates his or her own profile, which contains the personal information that the user chooses to include such as instant messaging IDs, birth date, gender, photos, location, occupation, phone model and network provider. This information is provided knowingly by user to be publicly viewable.

User-Posted Information

Our web site offers discussion forums, shoutbox, and other services both private and public. A user must remember that any information that is disclosed in public becomes public information. User must exercise caution when deciding to disclose his or her personal information.

Children

Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.

Usage Tracking

We track user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. We do break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser). We sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for our users.

### HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION

"E-mail this to a friend" Service

The email address of a registered user which we refer to as a basic user information will never be shared with or displayed to anyone. A user's email address will be used when a user chooses to use the "e-mail this to a friend" feature of our forums where user can electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking "e-mail this to a friend". The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose.

Sending Notifications

We send notifications to the user's email address relating to important announcement or his or her use of our service or web site. If the user so chooses, we will send alerts relating to his or her private messages and subscribed threads in the forums.

Sharing Of User Profile Information

The personal information of a registered user contained in his or her profile will be visible to all users of our web site, whether or not they are registered users.

Tracking Information

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for our users. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don't track which terms a particular user enters. Primarily, the click-stream data, HTTP protocol elements, search terms, and computer information that we obtained is used for system administration, research, and development.

### COOKIES

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on our web site. However, we do not and will not use cookies to collect private information from any user which they did not intentionally submit to us other than as stated in this Privacy Policy. We use both "session ID cookies" and "persistent cookies." We use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Note also that registered users may optionally use a cookie to remember their log in details in order to automatically log in to our website. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your web browsers "help" file. However, please note that, if you reject cookies or disable cookies in your web browser, you may not be able to participate actively in forums, polling, shoutbox, and arcade.

### THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISING

The ads appearing on this web site are delivered to users by our web advertising partners. Our web advertising partners may use cookies. Doing this allows the ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. We do not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed on the computer of any user of our website by the third-party ad servers or ad networks. This privacy notice covers the use of cookies by Mobilarian Forum only, and does not cover the use of cookies by any other party.

### LINKS

Mobilarian Forum contains links to other web sites. These include links that are placed there by us (such as in advertisements), as well as by other registered users. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any other website. We encourage our users to be aware of when they leave our web site, and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Mobilarian Forum website.

### SECURITY

Mobilarian Forum has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under its control. We operate secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our server has strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about its users.

### CONTACT US

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our privacy policy and/or practices, please [contact us](https://www.mobilarian.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#eb8a8f868285989f8a8d8dab86848982878a99828a85c5888486).
